# **Ngoc Anh Do**

7 ngo 169 Hoang Hoa Tham street, Ngoc Ha ward, Ba Dinh , DOB: 01-26-1995 +84964638900, nado.qemini62@qmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

**Senior Software Engineer** with over 9 years of proficiency in Machine learning, web and mobile. Successfully spearheaded projects across diverse sectors including Object detection, Stable diffusion, Python-based on Backend, automation & bot, Computer vision, Frontend using React and Vue.

### **EDUCATION**

SEP 2012-MAY 2016

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Hanoi University | Vietnam, VN

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

JUL 2021 - SEP 2022

Senior Software Engineer | Phibious | Hanoi, VN

- Developed and deployed Fastapi and Postgresql including RESTful APIs, data access, machine learning handling, logging, and error handling, as well as comprehensive testing and docker.
- Implemented Image segmentation and lots of filters using python and computer sciences, boosting quality of life analytic while ensuring robust code quality and functionality.
- Contributed to make lifeanalytics UI using React.
- Mentored 2 junior developers and prioritized cross-browser compatibility at the code level, leading to a 50% increase in user satisfaction and retention.

## OCT 2018 - APR 2021

Senior Software Engineer | Vietjetair | Hanoi, VN

- Developed machine learning models using popular libraries such as scikit-learn, TensorFlow, and PyTorch. These models have been trained on diverse datasets, allowing me to create accurate and effective solutions for a wide range of problem domains.
- Implemented lots of object detection, counting and tracking, OCR, Stable diffusion, face swap, etc.
- Generating/predicting gene based on experiment data using SVM and CNN.
- Integrated Databases with multiple database systems, including popular choices like PostgreSQL, MySQL, and MongoDB, has enabled me to work with various data storage solutions.
- Implemented automation of financial and employee management using Python and Data processing.

# JUL 2016 - SEP 2021

Senior Software Engineer | Phibious | Hanoi, VN

- Created and improved features for mobile and desktop web applications using React and React Native, resulting in a 25% increase in user engagement and retention.
- Utilized PostgreSQL for efficient data management, ensuring data integrity and high performance.
- Performed complex data analysis and manipulation using MySQL queries, functions, and procedures, such as data aggregation, filtering, sorting, and joining.
- Designed and implemented the frontend side using Bootstrap and jQuery, creating a responsive and user friendly interface for the web application.

# **SKILLS**

Python • torch • onnx • React.js • Next.js • React Native • Node.js • ASP.NET • PHP • Android • MongoDB • SQL • RESTful API • GraphQL • Javascript • Typescript • AWS • GCP • Git • Docker • jQuery • Bootstrap • SCSS • TailwindCSS • MUI